Guide to the WVBR records, 1946-2000s.
WVBR records, 1946-2000s.
- Audio / Visual material (Box 9-14)
  - Montclair High School, Winter Concert, B, 3/15/1968; tr8453 (Box 11)
  - Xmas Concert, Part 1, 12/20/1963; tr8454 (Box 11)
  - Blues Project, Bill Evans Trio, tr8455 (Box 11)
  - WOW, PWP, DP, April, 1974; tr8456 (Box 11)
  - 2nd Traffic Album, Mark Rudd, Wizard of Oz, 1968-69; tr8457 (Box 11)
  - Radio Workshop, History of ICB Act Reel, tr8458 (Box 11)
  - Joe Templeton, PSA’s, Dial-Up, tr8459 (Box 11)
  - WABC - FM, 12/25/1965; tr8460 (Box 11)
  - WABC, Z On the AIR, Perry Como, April, 1969; tr8461 (Box 11)
  - Aircheck, 11/13/1973; tr8462 (Box 11)
  - When I Die, Talkin Football Blues, tr8463 (Box 11)
  - Steve Post, tr8464 (Box 11)
  - Presidents & The Presidency, Candidates, Nixon Inaugural, 2/19/1969; tr8465 (Box 11)
  - Steve Schwartz’s Final Wonderland, WICB-FM, 5/2/1968; tr8466 (Box 11)
  - Bach Concert, WITR, tr8467 (Box 11)
  - Farinas, Grey Day, Van Ronk, Folksinger, tr8468 (Box 11)
  - Dvanron - Gamblers Blues, tr8469 (Box 11)
  - Queen, tr8470 (Box 11)
  - Barton Hall, tr8471 (Box 11)
  - VBR, Coverage Barton Occupation, tr8472 (Box 11)
  - WABC, Top 100, Smothers Bros., Chuck Leonard, 1967; tr8473 (Box 11)
  - Pres. & Presidency, Drugs In Ithaca, 1968; tr8474 (Box 11)
  - Steve Rathe Interview, WICB, Donovan, tr8475 (Box 11)
  - WICB, Paus of Dallas, 1968; tr8476 (Box 11)
  - VBR Folk Show, Maria McGyver Live, WICB, Bob Shechman, tr8477 (Box 11)
  - Tape Two, tr8478 (Box 11)
  - 1950’s Rock n Roll Music, Reel 1, Dec., 1958; tr8479 (Box 12)
  - Messiah Part 3, Beethoven #9, Part 1,2, Reel 3, Jan., 1968; tr8480 (Box 12)
  - Sound of Music, Reel 4, Dec., 1965; tr8481 (Box 12)
  - The Music Man, Reel 5, Dec., 1965; tr8482 (Box 12)
  - Mor, Folk, Boston Pops, Barbara Strisand, Reel 7, Oct., 1966; tr8483 (Box 12)
  - Jazz, Dave Brubeck, MJQ, Eddie Harris, Hames Moody, Andre Previn, Ahmad Jamal, Thelonius Monk, Reel 8, Oct., 1966; tr8484 (Box 12)
  - Light Classical, Boston Pops, Chicago Symphony, Marche, Nov., 1966; tr8485 (Box 12)
  - Slav Nutcracker Boston Pops Concert, Reel 9, 2/6/1968; tr8485 (Box 12)
  - Folk - Peter, Paul, & Mary, Concert, Reel 10, tr8486 (Box 12)
  - Chad Mitchell Trio, Peter, Paul, & Mary, Reel 20, tr8487 (Box 12)
  - Man of La Mancha, Camelot, Reel 25, tr8488 (Box 12)
  - Peter, Paul, & Mary, Gary Kaye, Stereo Stella, Reel 26, tr8489 (Box 12)
  - Mor TJB, PPM, Reel 29, tr8490 (Box 12)
  - Bound For Glory, Stereo Stella, Reel 30, May, 1968; tr8491 (Box 12)
  - Sorcerer’s Apprentice, Rite of Spring, Reel 33, April, 1968; tr8492 (Box 12)
  - VBR, Beethoven 9th, Mormon Tabernacle, Reel 34, 1968; tr8493 (Box 12)
  - Bach Organ Fugues, VBR Marathon, Reel 37, tr8494 (Box 12)
  - Kennedy 1, Reel 38, tr8495 (Box 12)
  - Kennedy 2, Reel 39, tr8496 (Box 12)
  - Kennedy 3, Reel 40, tr8497 (Box 12)
  - Kennedy 4, Reel 41, tr8498 (Box 12)
  - Firesage Theater, Waiting For The Electricman, Reel 46, Dec., 1968; tr8499 (Box 12)
  - The Mamas & The Papas, Golden Era 1 and 2, Reel 49, 2/17/1969; tr8500 (Box 12)
  - Judy Collins, Reel 50, 2/21/1969; tr8501 (Box 12)
  - Moody Blues, Vanilla Fudge, Reel 51, 2/25/1969; tr8502 (Box 12)
  - Reel 52, tr8503 (Box 12)
  - Herb Squire’s Last Show, Reel 53, 5/14/1967; tr8504 (Box 12)
  - I & E Friday Nite Entertainment, Reel 54, 4/11/1969; tr8505 (Box 12)
  - Phil Ochs, Pleasures of The Harbor, 4/16/1969; tr8506 (Box 12)
  - Story Lady, Drops, Reel 56, 5/2/1967; tr8507 (Box 12)
  - Goodbye, Columbus, The Association, Reel 57, 5/9/1969; tr8508 (Box 12)
  - Simon & Garfunkel, Wednesday Morning, 3AM, Reel 59, 5/10/1969; tr8509 (Box 12)
  - Arlo Guthrie, Pete Seeger on Tonight Show, Reel 60, 5/27/1969; tr8510 (Box 12)
  - Streisand, Little Jack Horner, Reel 65, tr8511 (Box 12)
  - PPM, tr8512 (Box 12)
  - D Beers, GI Resistance, Reel 66, tr8513 (Box 12)
  - Reel 67, tr8514 (Box 12)
  - Free Design, Heaven/Earth, Reel 68, tr8515 (Box 12)
  - WICB, WVBR, John Ernisse, Reel 69, tr8516 (Box 12)
  - Raphel Frubeck du Burgas, Cleo Orch & Choun, tr8517 (Box 12)
  - Ithaca Festival Song, 1987; tr8518 (Box 12)
  - Holy Cross Midnight Mass, 1975; tr8519 (Box 12)
  - Our Lady of Solace, Syracuse, 12/24/1976; tr8520 (Box 12)
  - Rondstadt 2, tr8521a (Box 13)
  - Joe Rickard & The Jubeetown String Band, 10/11/1976; tr8522a (Box 13)
  - Joe Rickard & The Jubee Rooty, 1/23/1977; tr8523 (Box 13)
  - Nick Seeger, Spring, 1976; tr8524a (Box 13)
  - Nick Seeger, 1/22/1978; tr8525a (Box 13)
  - Peabody, 2/27/1977; tr8526a (Box 13)
  - Henrie Family, Fall, 1978; tr8527a (Box 13)
  - Ed Holstein, Spring, 1978; tr8528a (Box 13)
  - Pearee Campbell, 2/13/1977; tr8529a (Box 13)
  - Steve Gillette & Cindy Maugsten, 1997; tr8530a (Box 13)
  - Peggy Haine, 11/14/1976; tr8531a (Box 13)
  - Peggy Haine, tr8532a (Box 13)
  - Peggy Haine, 5/14/1978; tr8533a (Box 13)
  - Jambalaya, 4/24/1978; tr8534a (Box 13)
  - Jambalaya, Reversed Stereo, 10/31/1976; tr8535a (Box 13)
  - Juggernaut, 12/5/1982; tr8536a (Box 13)
  - Juggernaut, 3rd Set, 12/5/1982; tr8537a (Box 13)
  - Debby McClatchy, 1st and 2nd Sets, Sept., 1977; tr8538a (Box 13)
  - Debby McClatchy, 3rd, tr8539a (Box 13)
  - Phil Shapiro, Nick, 9/26/1976; tr8540a (Box 13)
  - Bill Price, 7/28/1978; tr8541a (Box 13)
  - Conecttones, 9/5/1976; tr8542a (Box 13)
  - Good Mob, Still Standing Sampler, 1998; tr8543a (Box 13)
  - Andy Wallace, 3rd Set, 10/17/1982; tr8544a (Box 13)
  - Wander Beam, 11/12/1978; tr8545a (Box 13)
  - Christopher Woitak, tr8546a (Box 13)
  - Andy Wallace & Friends, Bound For Glory, 10/17/1982; tr8547a (Box 13)
  - Andy Wallace, 3rd Set, 10/17/1982; tr8548a (Box 13)
  - Robin & Linda, Spring, 1978; tr8549a (Box 13)
  - Robin & Linda, 1982/85; tr8550a (Box 13)
  - Stonehenge, Larry Watson, Naked Eye, tr8551a (Box 13)
  - Swaming Roots, 12/10/1977; tr8552a (Box 13)
  - Bill Steele, 3/20/1977; tr8553a (Box 13)
  - Bill Steele, 1976; tr8554a (Box 13)
  - Bill Steele, 11/18/1977; tr8555a (Box 13)
  - Bill Staines, 12/12/1976; tr8556a (Box 13)
  - John Sakin, 10/24/1976; tr8557a (Box 13)
  - 1st Mark Rust, Nov-77; tr8558a (Box 13)
  - Mark Rust, 1/29/1978; tr8559a (Box 13)
  - Mark Rust, tr8560a (Box 13)
  - Mark Rust, tr8561a (Box 13)
  - Small Change, tr8562a (Box 13)
  - Carellis, Moot of 2nd, 8/6/1977; tr8563a (Box 13)
  - Fun with Headsets Greatest Hits, 1981; tr8564a (Box 13)
  - Vega Parody, tr8565a (Box 13)
  - Cram Lake, Nick Seely, Hibert Folk Festival, tr8566a (Box 13)
  - Ronstadt I, tr8567a (Box 13)
  - Cranberry Lake, 10/17/1976; tr8568a (Box 13)
  - Todd Hobin at Nite Court, 9/23/1978; tr8569a (Box 13)
  - Fiction Bro’s, Desperado, Spring 1978; tr8570a (Box 13)
  - Cranberry Lake, 2/6/1977; tr8571a (Box 13)
  - Frostwater, 5/8/1977; tr8572a (Box 13)
  - Tim Tans, tom Rush, Unicorn, 12/5/1975; tr8573a (Box 13)
  - Desperado, 12/29/1978; tr8574a (Box 13)
  - Desperado, Destler, Bound For Glory, 1982; tr8575a (Box 13)
  - Desperado, Fiction Bros, 9/7/1978; tr8576a (Box 13)
  - Desperado at Under The Stone, 12/9/1978; tr8577a (Box 13)
  - Desperado at The Nine’s, 12/13/1978; tr8578a (Box 13)
  - Desperado at Under The Stone, Kenny Hall, Bound For Glory, 12/16/1978; tr8579a (Box 13)
  - Desperado at Strand, 9/9/1978; tr8580a (Box 13)
  - Desperado, Glenwood Pines, 12/5/1978; tr8581a (Box 13)
  - Desperado at Stanhope Inn, 12/7/1978; tr8582a (Box 13)
  - Unidentified, tr8583a (Box 13)
  - Tina Turner, tr8584a (Box 13)
  - A Wake-Up Call For the ‘90s, 1990; tr8585a (Box 13)
  - Dizzy Gillespie Sextet, Artic show, tr8586a (Box 13)
  - James Taylor, tr8587a (Box 13)
  - Paul Winter, 1st Half, tr8588a (Box 13)
  - Mother Freedom at Nite Court, Late, 1978; tr8589a (Box 13)
  - Doughboys, Crush, 1993; tr8590a (Box 13)
  - Howie Burson, Spring, 1978; tr8591a (Box 13)
  - Cranberry Lake, 12/3/1978; tr8592a (Box 13)
  - Bill Destter, 7/16/1978; tr8593a (Box 13)
  - Tom Rush, 3/30/1979; tr8594a (Box 13)
  - Tokyo, tr8595a (Box 13)
  - Linn Brown, Dean Brothers (Stagefight), tr8596a (Box 13)
  - Richard Belzer, tr8597a (Box 13)
  - Barry Manilow, If I Should Love Again, 1981; tr8598a (Box 13)
  - Green Bay, 8/10/1983; tr8599a (Box 13)
  - Green Bay, 8/11/1983; tr8600a (Box 13)
  - Bound For Glory, Clarisse DuBorgel, Mark Dix, tr8601a (Box 13)
  - John Bacley, 1/30/1977; tr8602a (Box 13)
  - George Winston, December; tr8603a (Box 13)
  - Howie Burson, 9/10/1978; tr8604a (Box 13)
  - Meatloaf, Bat Out of Hell, 1977; tr8605a (Box 13)
  - Sling By Slinge, tr8606a (Box 13)
  - Bill S, Goodness, tr8607a (Box 13)
  - Easter First Pass, tr8608a (Box 14)
- Cassette tapes (Box 14)
  - Marian, Aircheck,/Prod Demo, WKRT, tr8609a (Box 14)
  - Powerside, Platform Motion, Demo, tr8610a (Box 14)
  - Pink Floyd, Dark Side Of The Moon, 1973; tr8611a (Box 14)
  - Crossfire Choir, Interview, 1988; tr8612a (Box 14)
  - Mark Rust, Brooktondale (Allentown), tr8613a (Box 14)
  - Michael Manall, Aircheck, tr8614a (Box 14)
  - Mark Rust, Bound For Glory, tr8615a (Box 14)
  - Ellen Hertz at Piano Sage Chapel, tr8616a (Box 14)
  - Aurora, Studio C, tr8617a (Box 14)
  - Aurora, Studio C, tr8618a (Box 14)
  - Midnight Mass, Our Lady of Solace, Syracuse, 12/25/1976; tr8619a (Box 14)
  - Barry, TKO, CUBB, tr8620a (Box 14)
  - Bob Baker Kitchens, 7/7/1986; tr8621a (Box 14)
  - FM-93, Ski Report, tr8622a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8623a (Box 14)
  - This Sunday, Nov-86; tr8624a (Box 14)
  - This Sunday, 12/20/1986; tr8625a (Box 14)
  - SAREX, tr8626a (Box 14)
  - 5=45p, 41/2/1991; tr8627a (Box 14)
  - Bert’s Time Flex Slippin, 1990; tr8628a (Box 14)
  - Parachute Something, tr8629a (Box 14)
  - Uncle Fester Audition, tr8630a (Box 14)
  - Sarhal, 1986; tr8631a (Box 14)
  - Uncle Fester Audition, Kevin Farrelly, tr8632a (Box 14)
  - Hooters - Nervous Night, Steve Biatter, tr8633a (Box 14)
  - Top Sports, 3/29/1986; tr8634a (Box 14)
  - Jessica R Ettinger, tr8635a (Box 14)
  - Heart - Brigade, 1990; tr8636a (Box 14)
  - unidentified, tr8637a (Box 14)
  - IFI Audition, tr8638a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8639a (Box 14)
  - Frazier Smithon KLOS, 8 AM, Classic LA Radio, 7/5/1979; tr8640a (Box 14)
  - IFI Demo Techno Pop, tr8641a (Box 14)
  - WVBR Aircheck, 6:59a - 7:45a, 9/30/1981; tr8642a (Box 14)
  - WVBR Aircheck, 1:47p - 2:01p, 2:46p - 3:10p, 10/2/1981; tr8642a (Box 14)
  - FM93 News, tr8643a (Box 14)
  - Westwood One, The Twelve Hours of Christmas, tr8644a (Box 14)
  - 60’s at the Beeb Demo, tr8645a (Box 14)
  - Beatles, From Liverpool to Legend, tr8646a (Box 14)
  - Stay In School PSA’s, tr8647a (Box 14)
  - What Constitutes a Leader?, tr8648a (Box 14)
  - Soapmakers, The Yeti, 1998; tr8649a (Box 14)
  - Desert Island Discs, #37, 1990; tr8650a (Box 14)
  - VBR Aircheck, Heather, Midday, R + R for Modern Tunes, Early 90s; tr8651a (Box 14)
  - Marian Mathews. Wendy Miller, 93KRT, tr8652a (Box 14)
  - Andy Cohen, 4/16/1977; tr8653a (Box 14)
  - Andy Cohen, 3rd DBX, Bound For Glory, tr8654a (Box 14)
  - NYSP, Undercover Narcs, 4/2/1991; tr8655a (Box 14)
  - Rosallee sorrels, Bound For Glory, 2/3/1986; tr8656a (Box 14)
  - Carellis, 3rd, 8/6/1977; tr8657a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified Code-A-Phone message tape, tr8658a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8659a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8660a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8661a (Box 14)
  - Unidentified, tr8662a (Box 14)
- Some other WVBR collections, not within this collection
  - Student raid of WVBR collection, 1952 (Box 37-7-m.1055)
    Includes audio broadcast of the event on LP and CD. See also Deane W. Malott Papers, #3-9-651.
  - Robert Mayers WVBR audio collection., 1956-1960 (Box 35-9-3768 - 1)
    See finding aid here: http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA03768
  - Ted Osborn WVBR collection, 1959-1998 (Box 35-9-3512 - 1)
  - Bound for Glory records, #35-9-4277
    See finding aid here: http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA01739